desidieter.com 2018-07-17

# Privacy Policy | DesiDieter

[Home](http://www.desidieter.com/index.html)»Privacy Policy

|  |  | 

##  Privacy Policy  
  
---  
  
| 

#### Privacy Policy  
  
---  
At DesiDieter, we respect your privacy and believe you should be informed about how we collect, use and disclose your Personal Information.This Privacy Policy describes our practices regarding how we use and share with third parties Personal Information (as defined below ) that we collect on the Website.By visiting the DesiDieter.com website and any other URLs and websites administered by EZ-Healthline Pvt. Ltd., and its affiliates (collectively, the Website) submitting your Personal Information to us, you accept the practices described in this statement.The terms "you" and "user" as used herein refer to all individuals and/or entities accessing the Website for any reason.   
  
#### Terms of Use  
  
Your use of the Website is subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Term of Use, so please read this policy and the Terms of Use before using the Website.All terms with initial capital letters used in this Privacy Policy but not defined herein have the meanings given them in the Terms of Use.   
  
#### Age Requirement  
  
In order to use the Website you must be at least 18 years of age or the legal age to form a binding contract in your jurisdiction if that age is greater than 18 years of age.Please see the Terms of Use for additional information regarding this requirement.  
  
#### Personal Information  
  
The term Personal Information means information that identifies you as an individual, including your name, address, email address, telephone number, age, weight, and gender. We may ask you to submit Personal Information at various places on our Website, including by providing Registration Data, subscribing to a newsletter, or submitting feedback. DesiDieter also stores the information you enter about foods, activities, goals, and all other information collected in our online forms.  
The information you provide to DesiDieter may reveal, or allow others to identify your name, nationality, gender, age, or other aspects of your private life.  
We maintain lists of users and use the Personal Information on those lists to contact you or send you information you have requested or that we feel will be of interest to you.We may contact you via phone, email, or postal mail.We generally provide an option for you to choose not to receive these types of communications.However, even if you request not to be contacted by us, we reserve the right to use your contact information if we consider it necessary to send you information about the operation of the site, including information regarding the services you have signed up for on the Website or information about changes to our Privacy Policy.For more information about how to opt-out of receiving emails or third party offers, please click the Unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email sent to you by DesiDieter.   
Posts submitted to the Community Pages are not confidential and may be viewed by other users and the general public.  
  
#### Non-Personally Identifying Information  
  
We may also collect information automatically about the use of the Website, through, for example,cookies or IP addresses (as described below).DesiDieter also archives log files and uses non-personally identifying information in aggregate form to detect errors with the Website, identify security issues, and build higher quality, more useful online services by performing statistical analyses of the collective characteristics and behavior of DesiDieter users, and measure demographics and interests in connection with specific areas of the Website. We may provide such statistical data to our advertisers, affiliates and other current and potential business  

| 

## Members Login

## DesiDieter Expert Chat  

---  
  
|   |    
---|---  
| Veg Wholesome Meal

2 Rice flour bhakri + 1 katori radish veg + 1 katori corn and bean salad + buttermilk  
  
Get Eat Smart Alert in Your Inbox  
  
News & Articles

DesiDieter does not have a fitness trainer, anymore. We obse...
